

Rafael A. Sánchez #75, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic 10147

+1 (829) 479-9303

josbel.luna.r@gmail.com

@josbeldev

in josbel-luna

SKILLS

JavaScript React
Advanced Advanced

Testing TypeScript
Advanced Intermediate

NodeJS Ruby On Rails
Intermediate Intermediate

Angular Intermediate

LANGUAGES

English Spanish Fluent Native Tongue

HOBBIES

Playing Tennis

Reading Books on Kindle

CERTIFICATIONS

Linux Essentials

Microsoft

Associated

Microsoft

Microsoft Technology

Linux Professional Institute	Αρι 11 20 1 3
Professional Scrum Master II Scrum.org	April 2019
Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals Microsoft	February 2019
Professional Scrum Master I Scrum.org	February 2019
Microsoft Certified Professional	August

Josbel Luna

Full-Stack Web Developer

I'm a full-stack software engineer passionate about building high-performant, accessible websites. Most experienced in front-end development using React and Angular, and with a good amount of experience in back-end development with NodeJS, Ruby on Rails, and .Net Core.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BairesDev

Full-Stack Engineer

(November 2020 - Present)

Worked on the consumer site for an auto repair company located in San Francisco, CA. Helped the company to migrate and create new modules with new cutting-edge design, both in the backend (Ruby on Rails/GraphQL) and Front-End (React/Sass). Also, I helped the team in many other ways, such as optimizing web performance and accessibility, improving developer experiences and dev tools, etc.

Vivial

Software Engineer

(January 2020 - November 2020)

 Developed CMS APIs (Node, Express) and UI (React, Sass) with cloud technologies (AWS) and search engines (Elasticsearch) for a 100-year marketing company located in Bloomington · MN. I worked on migrating both public and admin sites from legacy ones.

Truenorth

Sr. Software Developer

(April 2019 - January 2020)

 Worked with the Puerto Rico Government for a website to manage insurance collections, using .Net Core as the backend and UI Angular for the front-end. My main job was integrating the policy and payment information from a public-facing app to pay business insurance. I also was part of the migration of a new platform to manage Government scholarships.

Marítima Dominicana

Sr. Software Developer

(June 2016 - April 2019)

 Developed financial and information websites made with .Net Core and AngularJS/2+ for a local shipping company. I maintained a large code base of apps, including billing, collections, documentation, etc. Also, I developed a new mobile and web application to organize and display cargo container warehouses.

ESC Group

April 2019

2017

August

2017

Mobile Developer

(March 2015 - June 2016)

• Develop mobile apps (Android) for monitoring and controlling smart bulbs. I also created APIs on top of ASP.NET to fulfill the app functionalities.

EDUCATION

UNAPEC	(January 2017 - July 2020)
Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering	A+
Technological Institute of the Americas Associate Degree in Mechatronic Technology	(December 2013 - August 2016) A+

REFERENCES

Claudio Ruíz	Jonathan Pérez	Sergio Cabrera
Engineering Manager,	Business Analyst, Marítima	Application Manager,
Marítima Dominicana	Dominicana	Truenorth
+1 (829) 638-9454	+1 (786) 217-2462	+1 (829) 723-4900